stdtestexpress.com 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy - STD Test Express

We take your privacy very seriously. We believe in protecting your information in the same way we want ours protected. Analyte Physicians Group, S.C. and its authorized agents (including Analyte Health, Inc.) (collectively, "Analyte," "we" or "us"), encourage you to become familiar with this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions of Use. 

This Privacy Policy describes what information we collect about you, how we collect it, how we use it, with whom we may share it, and what choices you have regarding it, on our website www.stdtestexpress.com. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is a part of the Terms and Conditions of Use of our website (the "Site"). We encourage you to become familiar with this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions of Use. By accessing and using the Site, you agree that you have read and understand this Privacy Policy and that you accept and consent to the privacy practices (and any uses and disclosures of information about you) that are described in this Privacy Policy.

Analyte Health has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe's program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, www.stdtestexpress.com and does not cover information that may be collected through any mobile applications and downloads.

TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at info@apgservices.com. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe here.

### What information do we collect, and how?

We may collect certain identifying information from or about you in connection with your use of or submissions to the Site, including, but not limited to, your name, address, date of birth, email addresses, health information, health plan ("Plan") information and credit card number (together, "Collected Information"). Any health information about you will be collected in the course of providing services to you via the Site and telephone consultations. Our use of such health information is governed by our Notice of Privacy Practices. In addition, we may retain the content of, and metadata regarding, any correspondence you may have with us or our representatives, regardless of the mode of communication by which such correspondence was made. This information helps us to improve the Site and the online content, materials, and services that we make available on the Site, and to more effectively and efficiently respond to both current and future inquiries.

As with many other websites, the web servers used to operate the Site may collect certain data pertaining to you and the equipment and communications method that you use to access the Internet and our Site and store it in log files. For security reasons and to confirm the integrity of the Site, we may combine components of these data with Collected Information, which may identify you. Unless otherwise described in this Privacy Policy or our Terms and Conditions of Use, such identifying information will be used solely for our business purposes. In addition, the information we collect may reveal such things as the Internet protocol ("IP") address assigned to your computer, specific pages that you accessed on the Site or prior to visiting the Site, and the length of time you spent at the Site. We may use this information to help administer the Site and the servers that provide the Site, generate statistical information, monitor and analyze Site traffic and usage patterns, and improve the Site's content and content delivery, including any online content, materials, and services that we describe or make available on the Site.

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Analyte Health, our marketing and analytics partners. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for remembering user settings and items added to our shopping cartUsers can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. 

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests.  If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking here. Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads.  You will continue to receive generic ads.

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Analyte. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

Our Web site includes widgets, such as Google Maps and embedded video players. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

In addition, our Site may use a third party web analytics service. These features may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, and scrolling activity as you navigate through the website. This Site does not use the feature to collect any personally identifiable information entered in this website or have the ability to view personally identifiable or health information. Furthermore, we do not track your browsing habits across websites we do not own. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. You can choose to disable the Service here.

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at info@apgservices.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

### How will we use the information you provide us?

In addition to the uses described above or in our Terms and Conditions of Use, we may use the information that we collect from or about you to analyze and improve the content, materials and services that we make available on the Site, to notify you of changes made to the Site, to evaluate user needs and customize the Site content delivered to you according to those needs, to send you promotional materials that you request from us, and for other legitimate and lawful business purposes. If you contact us for support or assistance, we may use information about you or your system that you provide or that we collect for purposes such as verifying whether your system meets the minimum requirements needed to use the Site and our various services. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. We may store Collected Information in the United States, or we may transfer it to other countries.

If you wish to subscribe to our promotional emails, we will use your name and email address to send them to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our promotional emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us at info@apgservices.com.

### With whom do we share the information we collect?

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy or the Notice of Privacy Practices. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may share Collected Information with our authorized agents in order to provide services to you, and for any other lawful business reasons. If all or part of Analyte is sold, merged, or otherwise transferred to another entity, we may transfer Collected Information to such entity as part of that transaction. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

We may disclose Collected Information to the proper authorities if we become subject to a subpoena or court order or if we are otherwise legally required to disclose such information. We may also use and disclose information about you to establish or exercise our legal rights, to enforce the Terms and Conditions of Use, to assert and defend against legal claims, or if we believe such disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding actual or suspected illegal or fraudulent activities or potential threats to the physical safety or well-being of any person.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as permitted by law and only as necessary to provide these services to us.

### What choices do you have?

When corresponding with Analyte or our representatives, or when making a request for information or otherwise interacting with us or others through the Site, you choose what information to supply, what questions or comments to submit, whether you wish to receive further information, and by what method of communication such information should be delivered. Please take care to share only such information as is needed or that you believe is appropriate. You are under no obligation to provide us with personally identifiable information, but without it we may not be able to provide you the products or services you request. You may contact us as indicated below if at any time you would like to ask us about our data collection practices and our information security policy.

If your personally identifiable information ("PII") changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend your PII, delete inaccuracies or deactivate your web accessible account by calling us at 866.660.2593.

### How do we protect information collected about you?

Analyte maintains certain commercially reasonable security measures to protect Collected Information, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our site, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). However, the storage and communication of Collected Information can never be completely secure. Hence we do not guarantee that information that you transmit or otherwise supply to us, or any communications conducted on or through the Site, is or will be totally secure. If you become aware of any breach of Site security, this Privacy Policy, or the Terms and Conditions of Use, please notify us immediately.

From time to time, we may change our privacy practices and this Privacy Policy, because of changes in relevant and applicable legal or regulatory requirements, our business practices, or in our attempts to better serve your needs and those of our other customers. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### Our commitment to your privacy

In addition to this Privacy Policy, Analyte provides a Notice of Privacy Practices to everyone who becomes a patient of Analyte through this site. This Notice, sometimes referred to as a "HIPAA Notice," describes how health information about you may be used and disclosed and how you can get access to this information. In this Notice, we describe the ways that we may use and disclose health information about our patients. This Notice describes your rights as our patient and our obligations regarding the use and disclosure of Personal Health Information (PHI). We encourage you to read this Notice and know your rights. If you would like more information regarding your privacy, please refer to our Notice of Privacy Practices.

### Contact Us

We take your privacy seriously. If you have questions, concerns, or feedback regarding the privacy of your personal and health information, you may contact our Privacy Officer at:

**Analyte Health**  
328 South Jefferson Street  
Suite 770  
Chicago, IL 60661

(888) 723.6082 

If you have a question that is medical in nature, about how our process works, or about service-related issues, please call us at [(866) 660-2593](tel:\(866\) 660-2593)(866) 660-2593 and speak with a Care Advisor. 

BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND AND CONSENT TO OUR PRIVACY PRACTICES AND TO THE USES AND DISCLOSURES OF INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU, AND YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE Terms and Conditions of Use APPLICABLE TO YOU. 

Updated July 1, 2015 Analyte Health, Inc. 

Copyright © 2015 Analyte Health, Inc.
